<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="es">
<head>
<title>Mi primera WEB 🌟</title>
</head>
<body>
    <h1>Mi primera WEB (Th1)</h1>
    <h2>Segundo titulo (h2)</h2>
    <h5>Tercer titulo (h5)</h5>
    
    <p> <em><strong>What is Lorem Ipsum?</strong></em> <i>Lorem Ipsum</i> is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry.<br>
    Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a <br>
    galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.<br> 
    It has survived not only five centuries, but also the leap into electronic typesetting, remaining essentially unchanged.<br> 
    It was popularised in the 1960s with the release of Letraset sheets containing Lorem Ipsum passages, and more recently<br>
    with desktop publishing software like Aldus PageMaker including versions of Lorem Ipsum.<br><hr>
    </p>
    <h2>Segundo titulo (h2)</h2>
    <p> <em><strong>What is Lorem Ipsum?</strong></em> <i>Lorem Ipsum</i> is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry.<br>
        Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a <br>
        galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.<br> 
        It has survived not only five centuries, but also the leap into electronic typesetting, remaining essentially unchanged.<br> 
        It was popularised in the 1960s with the release of Letraset sheets containing Lorem Ipsum passages, and more recently<br>
        with desktop publishing software like Aldus PageMaker including versions of Lorem Ipsum.<br><hr>
        </p>
        <h2>Segundo titulo (h2)</h2>
        <p> <em><strong>What is Lorem Ipsum?</strong></em> <i>Lorem Ipsum</i> is simply dummy text of the printing and typesetting industry.<br>
            Lorem Ipsum has been the industry's standard dummy text ever since the 1500s, when an unknown printer took a <br>
            galley of type and scrambled it to make a type specimen book.<br> 
            It has survived not only five centuries, but also the leap into electronic typesetting, remaining essentially unchanged.<br> 
            It was popularised in the 1960s with the release of Letraset sheets containing Lorem Ipsum passages, and more recently<br>
            with desktop publishing software like Aldus PageMaker including versions of Lorem Ipsum.<br><hr>
            </p>
</body>
</html>
